Guide to the Stanford Channel Master Videorecordings
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Videos (Box 1)
  - Stanford Presents
    - 109th Commencement at Stanford, 00-130 (Box 23)
    - The 110th Opening Convocation at Stanford University, 00-131 (Box 23)
    - The Inauguration and Investiture of John Hennessy as the Tenth President of Stanford University, 00-132 (Box 23)
    - The 21st Century Lawyer: The Future of Legal Education, 00-133 (Box 23)
    - Making the Most of the Internet Economy, 00-134 (Box 23)
    - Making the Most of the Internet Economy, 00-134 (Box 23)
    - Bridging the Digital Divide, 00-135/a (Box 23)
    - Bridging the Digital Divide, 00-135/b (Box 23)
    - Bridging the Digital Divide, 00-135/c (Box 24)
    - Living History: Women from Civil Rights to Black Power tape #1, 01-136 (Box 24)
    - Living History: Women from Civil Rights to Black Power tape #2, 01-136 (Box 24)
    - Taking Stock, 01-137 (Box 24)
    - Republic.com: A Discussion of Cass Sunstein's New Book, 01-138 (Box 24)
    - The Second Amendment: History, Evidence, and the Constitution. Keynote Address, 01-139/a (Box 24)
    - The Second Amendment: History, Evidence, and the Constitution. Keynote: How Americans Became an Armed People tape #1, 01-139/b (Box 24)
    - The Second Amendment: History, Evidence, and the Constitution. Keynote: How Americans Became an Armed People tape #2, 01-139/b (Box 24)
    - The Second Amendment: History, Evidence and the Constitution The Seond Amendment Original Meanings, 01-139/c (Box 24)
    - The Second Amendment: History, Evidence, and the Constitution. Firearms Regulations: Present and Future, 01-139/d (Box 24)
    - Difficult Dialogues: A Stanford Forum on Gender and Ethnicity, Aging in the 21st Century tape #1, 01-141 (Box 24)
    - Difficult Dialogues: A Stanford Forum on Gender and Ethnicity, Aging in the 21st Century tape #2, 01-141 (Box 24)
    - Infectious Disease Surveillance: Bio-Terrorism and Global Security, 01-142 (Box 24)
    - 20 Years of Feminist Studies at Stanford Part One, 01-143/a (Box 24)
    - 20 Years of Feminist Studies at Stanford Part Two, 01-143/b (Box 25)
    - 20 Years of Feminist Studies at Stanford Part Three, 01-143/c (Box 25)
    - 20 Years of Feminist Studies at Stanford Part Four, 01-143/d (Box 25)
    - 20 Years of Feminist Studies at Stanford Part Five, 01-143/e (Box 25)
  - The Arts at Stanford
    - Stanford String Quartet: Open Rehearsal, 95-201 (Box 25)
    - Innovative Architecture, 1995: Program #2, 95-202 (Box 25)
    - Stegner Fellows' Reading, 95-203 (Box 25)
    - Innovative Architecture, 1995: Program #1, 95-204 (Box 25)
    - Chicano Art, 95-205 (Box 25)
    - Stanford String Quartet: In Performance, 95-206 (Box 25)
    - The Bing Music Series, 95-207 (Box 25)
    - Rita Dove, Poet Laureate, 96-208 (Box 26)
    - Dreams of a City: Dancing on the Brink, 96-209 (Box 26)
    - Dreams of a City: Circle in the Dirt, 96-210 (Box 26)
    - Any Space Between Shadows, 96-211 (Box 26)
    - Real Original Thinker, 96-212 (Box 26)
    - Hayden Carruth: Poet of Darkness and Light, 96-213 (Box 26)
    - A Tribute to Count Basie, 96-214 (Box 26)
    - Song of Survival, 96-215 (Box 26)
    - Innovative Architecture, 1996: Program #1 The Temporal in Architecture, 96-216 (Box 26)
    - Innovative Architecture, 1996: Program #2, The Temporal in Architecture, 96-217 (Box 26)
    - Innovative Architecture, 1996: The Temporal in Architecture, 96-218 (Box 26)
    - Innovative Architecture, 1996: Program #4, The Temporal in Architecture, 96-219 (Box 27)
    - Jim Crow On Trial: Voices From The Montgomery Bus Boycott, 96-220 (Box 27)
    - Stanford Improvisors Theatresports, 96-221 (Box 27)
    - Kurt Elling Quartet, 96-222 (Box 27)
    - Madeline Eastman Jazz Quartet, 96-223 (Box 27)
    - Neglected Glory: Africa's Mosque of Djenne and Other Adobe Treasures, 96-224 (Box 27)
    - Robert Hass, Poet Laureate, 96-225 (Box 27)
    - University Singers Fall Concert, 1996, 96-226 (Box 27)
    - Original Winter One Acts, 97-227/a (Box 27)
    - Original Winter One Acts, 97-227/b (Box 27)
    - Original Winter One Acts, 97-227/c (Box 27)
    - Franz Peter Schubert: A 200th Birthday Celebration Concert, 97-228 (Box 27)
    - A Reading by Susan Howe, 97-229 (Box 27)
    - A Widow for One Year, 97-230 (Box 27)
    - For the Love of Music, 97-231 (Box 28)
    - A Reading by Margaret Drabble, 97-232 (Box 28)
    - Innovative Architecture 1997: Architecture and Landscape as Medium, 97-233 (Box 28)
    - Innovative Architecture 1997: Architecture and Landscape as Medium, 97-234 (Box 28)
    - Innovative Architecture III: Architecture and Landscape as a Medium tape #1, 97-235 (Box 28)
    - Innovative Architecture III: Architecture and Landscape as a Medium, 97-235 (Box 28)
    - Innovative Architecture 1997: Architecture and Landscape as Medium, 97-236 (Box 28)
    - Stanford Woodwind Quintet: Tenth Anniversary Concert, 97-237 (Box 28)
    - An Evening of Poetry with Eavan Boland and Denise Levertov, 97-238 (Box 28)
    - Stanford String Quartet: Spring Concert, 1997, 97-239 (Box 28)
    - SIMPS '97!, 97-240 (Box 28)
    - Chicano Theater in America: Acts of Protest and Affirmation: The Indigenous Roots of Chicano and Mexicano Teatristas, 97-241 (Box 28)
    - The Spirit of Saroyan, Part 1, 97-243/a (Box 29)
    - The Spirit of Saroyan, Part 2, 97-243/b (Box 29)
    - Kellye Gray in Concert, 97-244 (Box 29)
    - The Design Eye, 97-245 (Box 29)
    - Mountains and Rivers Without End tape #1, 97-246 (Box 29)
    - Mountains and Rivers Without End, 97-246 (Box 29)
    - 1997 Lane Lectures: Robert Creeley, 97-247 (Box 29)
    - University Singers: 1997 Fall Concert, 97-248 (Box 29)
    - The Music Guild Presents: The First-Ever All-Campus Faculty Talent Show tape #1, 98-249 (Box 29)
    - The Music Guild Presents: The First-Ever All-Campus Faculty Talent Show tape #2, 98-249 (Box 29)
    - Improvisation: Useful Tools for Everyday Living, 98-250 (Box 29)
    - Original Winter One Acts, 1998, 98-251/a (Box 29)
    - Original Winter One Acts, 1998, 98-251/b (Box 29)
    - Original Winter One Acts, 1998, 98-251/c (Box 30)
    - A Tribute to Denise Levertov, 98-252 (Box 30)
    - Lane Lecture: Grace Paley, 98-253 (Box 30)
    - Innovations tape #1, 98-254 (Box 30)
    - Innovations tape #2, 98-254 (Box 30)
    - The Queen's History of the King of the World, 98-255 (Box 30)
    - Lane Lecture: Robert Pinsky, 98-256 (Box 30)
    - Innovative Architecture IV: The Dream in Architecture and Landscape, Program #2 tape #1, 98-258 (Box 30)
    - Innovative Architecture IV: The Dream in Architecture and Landscape, Program #2 tape #2, 98-258 (Box 30)
    - Innovative Architecture IV: The Dream in Architecture and Landscape tape #1, 98-259 (Box 30)
    - Innovative Architecture IV: The Dream in Architecture and Landscape tape #2, 98-259 (Box 30)
    - Innovative Architecture IV: The Dream in Architecture and Landscape, 98-260 (Box 30)
    - Will Bernard 4-Tet tape #1, 98-261 (Box 30)
    - Will Bernard 4-Tet tape #2, 98-261 (Box 30)
    - Innovative Architecture: The Dream in Architecture and Landscape, Program #1, 98-257 (Box 30)
    - Ledisi tape #1, 98-262 (Box 31)
    - Ledisi tape #2, 98-262 (Box 31)
    - Columna B in Concert tape #1, 98-263 (Box 31)
    - Columna B in Concert tape #2, 98-263 (Box 31)
    - The Lane Lectures: John le Carre, 98-264 (Box 31)
    - Presidential Reading Series: Dorothy Allison, 98-265 (Box 31)
    - A Man in Full, 98-266 (Box 31)
    - Presidential Reading: Li-Young Lee, 99-267 (Box 31)
    - Original Winter One Acts, 1999, 99-268 (Box 31)
    - Lane Lecture: Peter Carey, 99-269 (Box 31)
    - Lane Lecture: Sharon Olds, 99-270 (Box 31)
    - Innovative Architecture and Landscape V, Program 1 tape #1, 99-271 (Box 31)
    - Innovative Architecture and Landscape V, Program 1 tape #2, 99-271 (Box 31)
    - Innovative Architecture and Landscape V, Program 2, 99-272 (Box 31)
    - Innovative Architecture and Landscape V, Program 3, 99-273 (Box 32)
    - Innovative Architecture and Landscape V, Program 4, 99-274 (Box 32)
    - Looking Again at Jackson Pollock, 99-275 (Box 32)
    - President's Reading Series: Arundhati Roy, 99-276 (Box 32)
    - Stanford Jazz: Marcus Shelby Trio tape #1, 99-277 (Box 32)
    - Stanford Jazz: Marcus Shelby Trio tape #2, 99-277 (Box 32)
    - Stanford Jazz: Sandy Cressman's Homenagem Brasileira tape #1, 99-278 (Box 32)
    - Stanford Jazz: Sandy Cressman's Homenagem Brasileira tape #2, 99-278 (Box 32)
    - President's Reading Series: Sherman Alexie, 99-279 (Box 32)
    - Lane Lecture: Peter Matthiessen, 99-280 (Box 32)
    - TheatreSports: Stanford Improvisors vs. Bay Area TheatreSports, 96-221 (Box 32)
    - Chicano Theater in America, Part 2: The Life and Death of Emiliano Zapata and Somos Uno., 97-242 (Box 32)
    - President's Reading Series: Allegra Goodman, 00-281 (Box 33)
    - Lane Lecture: Tim O'Brien, 00-282 (Box 33)
    - Short Trip Home: A Lively Arts Special, 00-283 (Box 33)
    - Scott Turow: A Reading, 00-284 (Box 33)
    - Innovative Architecture VI: Light in Architecture and Landscape, 00-285 (Box 33)
    - Innovative Architecture Series: Light in Architecture and Landscape II, 00-286 (Box 33)
    - Innovative Architecture: Light in Architecture and Landscape, 00-287 (Box 33)
    - Innovative Architecture: Light in Architecture and Landscape IV, 00-288 (Box 33)
    - Finnegans Awake: A Day of Irish Poetry, 00-289/a (Box 33)
    - Finnegans Awake: A Day of Irish Poetry, 00-289/b (Box 33)
    - Finnegans Awake: A Day of Irish Poetry, 00-289/c (Box 33)
    - President's Reading Series: Vikram Seth, 00-290 (Box 33)
    - NLS Trio with Paul Nagel tape #1, 00-291 (Box 34)
    - NLS Trio with Paul Nagel tape #2, 00-291 (Box 34)
    - Lane Lecture: Robert Stone, 00-292 (Box 34)
    - A Poetry Reading in Memory of Yvor Winters, 00-293 (Box 34)
    - Contemporary Poets: Fanny Howe, 00-294 (Box 34)
    - Architecture as Landscape: Landscape as Architecture -- Zvi Hecker, Works in Progress, 01-202 (Box 34)
    - Architecture as Landscape: Landscape as Architecture II: A Promenade Through Dani Karavan's Work, 01-203 (Box 34)
    - Architecture as Landscape: Landscape as Architecture: The "Planetary-Garden.", 01-204 (Box 34)
    - Architecture as Landscape, Landscape as Architecture, 01-205 (Box 34)
    - President's Reading Series: Stuart Dybek, 01-206 (Box 34)
    - From One Farm to Another: Stanford Students Design Mexican Orphanages "Welcome, Introduction to Course and Public Relations" and "Introduction to Unifying Theme for Rancho Santa Marta", 01-207/a (Box 34)
    - From One Farm to Another: Stanford Students Design Mexican Orphanages "Rancho Santa Marta Girls Home", 01-207/b (Box 34)
    - From One Farm to Another: Stanford Students Design Mexican Orphanages "Rancho Santa Marta Play Ground", 01-207/c (Box 34)
    - From One Farm to Another: Stanford Students Design Mexican Orphanages "Rancho Santa Marta Children's Art Project", 01-207/d (Box 35)
    - From One Farm to Another: Stanford Students Design Mexican Orphanages "San Vicente Center", 01-207/e (Box 35)
    - From One Farm to Another: Stanford Students Design Mexican Orphanages "San Vicente Center Care Takers home", 01-207/f (Box 35)
    - From One Farm to Another: Stanford Students Design Mexican Orphanages "Water Elements at San Vicente Center", 01-207/g (Box 35)
    - From One Farm to Another: Stanford Students Design Mexican Orphanages "Closing Reflections and Lessons Learned"., 01-207/h (Box 35)
    - President's Reading Series: Rafael Campo, 01-295 (Box 35)
    - Contemporary Poets: June Jordan, 01-296 (Box 35)
    - A Site for Sight: Monet in his Garden at Giverny, 01-297 (Box 35)
    - Another Book Peace, 01-298 (Box 35)
    - A Reading by John Ashbery, 01-299 (Box 35)
  - The Life of the Mind
    - The Enola Gay Controversy, 95-301 (Box 35)
    - The Origins of Humans, 95-302 (Box 35)
    - Responding to Racial Injustice, Part 1: What's Wrong with Color Blindness?, 95-303 (Box 36)
    - Responding to Racial Injustice: What's Right About Race Consciousness?, 95-304 (Box 36)
    - The Shape of the Universe, 95-305 (Box 36)
    - Human Guinea Pigs? The Ethics of Radiation Experiments On Humans, 95-306 (Box 36)
    - Great Teachers, Great Texts: Nancy Packer on William Faulkner, 95-307 (Box 36)
    - Great Teachers, Great Texts: Tragedy of Hamlet, Prince of Denmark, 95-309 (Box 36)
    - Great Teachers, Great Texts: Diane Middlebrook on Sexton and Plath tape #1, 95-310 (Box 36)
    - Great Teachers, Great Texts: Diane Middlebrook on Sexton and Plath tape #2, 95-310 (Box 36)
    - Good and Evil, 95-311 (Box 36)
    - Conflicting Visions of a Good Society, 95-312 (Box 36)
    - Cosmic Impacts: Chicken Little Was Right, 95-313 (Box 36)
    - Great Teachers, Great Texts: Robert Polhemus on Dickens, 95-308 (Box 36)
    - Inter-Group Violence: Preventing Conflicts from Exploding Into War, 95-316 (Box 37)
    - The Last Word: Two Lectures on Reason, 96-317 (Box 37)
    - The Nature of Nature, 96-322 (Box 37)
    - Come the Millenium, Where the University?, 95-314 (Box 37)
    - Friendship, 95-315 (Box 37)
    - The Last Word: Two Lectures on Reason, Program #2, 96-318 (Box 37)
    - Dinosaur in a Haystack: Reflections on Natural History, 96-319 (Box 37)
    - The Great Altar of Pergamon, 96-320 (Box 37)
    - Black Liberation Movements, 96-321 (Box 37)
    - Reflections on the Discovery of the Tau Lepton, 96-323 (Box 37)
    - Social Justice in the Age of Identity Politics: From Redistribution to Recognition, 96-324 (Box 37)
    - Social Justice in the Age of Identity Politics: Toward an Integrated Conception of Justice, 96-325 (Box 38)
    - Satan and All His Angels: How Christians Came to Demonize Jews, Pagans and Heretics, 96-326 (Box 38)
    - The Invention of the Airplane, 96-327 (Box 38)
    - Sex, Lies and Theater: Shakespeare and His Times, 96-328 (Box 38)
    - Life on Mars? Laboratory Measurements of Extraterrestrial Visitors, 96-329 (Box 38)
    - Lasers in Your Life: Thirty Years of Coherent Light at Stanford, 96-330 (Box 38)
    - Volcanic Hazards, 96-331 (Box 38)
    - Some Perspectives on Energy and Climate Change, 96-332 (Box 38)
    - Immigrants Who Settled in California: Where and Why?, 96-333 (Box 38)
    - The Living Language of Genesis, 96-334 (Box 38)
    - Infonauts in Cyberspace, 96-335 (Box 38)
    - The Selfish Meme, 97-336 (Box 39)
    - Gospel Choirs: Psalms of Survival in an Alien Land Called Home, 97-337 (Box 39)
    - The Chinese Economy, 97-338 (Box 39)
    - Music and the Holocaust, 97-339 (Box 39)
    - Music and the Holocaust, Program #2, 97-340 (Box 39)
    - Democracy, Race and Nationality in the 19th Century America, Program #1: The American Revolution and Its Legacy, 97-341 (Box 39)
    - Democracy, Race and Nationality in the 19th Century America, Program #2: The Age of Civil War and Emancipation, 97-342 (Box 39)
    - Innovations in Learning Technology Design, 97-343 (Box 39)
    - Hitler and the Decisions for the Final Solution, 97-344 (Box 39)
    - Women and Reform in Modern America, 97-345 (Box 39)
    - Women and Reform in Modern America, 97-345 (Box 39)
    - Bloomsbury in Sussex: The Way of the Writer, The Way of the Artist, 97-346 (Box 39)
    - The Practice of Moral Judgment, Program #1: Responsibility and Moral Competence, 97-347 (Box 40)
    - The Practice of Moral Judgment, Program #2: Can Virtue Be Taught?, 97-348 (Box 40)
    - Slavery and the History of Evil, 97-350 (Box 40)
    - Writing the Speculative: A Symposium on Poetry and Knowledge, Program #1: Thought In/About Poetry, 97-351/a (Box 40)
    - Writing the Speculative: A Symposium on Poetry and Knowledge, Program #2: Philosophical Poetics, 97-351/b (Box 40)
    - Writing the Speculative: A Symposium on Poetry and Knowledge, Program #3: The Status of the Poet tape #1, 97-351/c (Box 40)
    - Writing the Speculative: A Symposium on Poetry and Knowledge, Program #3: The Status of the Poet, 97-351/c (Box 40)
    - The Writer's Craft, 97-352 (Box 40)
    - Justice Thurgood Marshall: Warrior Within the System, 97-353 (Box 40)
    - Search for Consciousness: Philos, Neuroscience and Psychology Program #1: To Have but Not to Hold, 97-354/a (Box 40)
    - Search for Consciousness: Philos, Neuroscience and Psychology Program #2: Thought Without Language, Thought Without Awareness, 97-354/b (Box 40)
    - From Cheap Thriller to High Art: The New Respectability of the American Detective Novel, 97-349 (Box 40)
    - Search for Consciousness: Philos, Neuroscience and Psychology Program #3: The Blind Leading the Sighted, and Learning from Their Pupils, 97-354/c (Box 41)
    - Search for Consciousness: Philosophy, Neuroscience and Psychology Program #4: Imaging the Imageless, 97-354/d (Box 41)
    - Boyhood: A reading from the memoir of J.M. Coetzee, 97-355 (Box 41)
    - Music: Light, Sound and Mathematics tape #1, 97-356 (Box 41)
    - Music: Light, Sound and Mathematics, 97-356 (Box 41)
    - Christian Conviction in a Pluralist Society, 97-357 (Box 41)
    - The Impact of the Slave Trade on African History, 98-358 (Box 41)
    - Constructing a Trans-National Jewish Culture, Program #1, 98-359/a (Box 41)
    - Constructing a Trans-National Jewish Culture, Program #2, 98-359/b (Box 41)
    - Constructing a Trans-National Jewish Culture, Program #3, 98-359/c (Box 41)
    - Two Works in Progress: The Gates Project for Central Park in New York City and The Over the River Project for the Arkansas River in Colorado, 98-360 (Box 41)
    - Interiority, 98-361 (Box 41)
    - The Ironic Construction of Civic America, 98-362/a (Box 41)
    - Democracy Unravelled: America in the Late 20th Century, 98-362/b (Box 42)
    - The Danger of Social Experience: Suffering in Local and Global Perspectives, 98-363/a (Box 42)
    - The Moral, the Political and the Medical: Ethnography of Engagement, 98-363/b (Box 42)
    - The Way We Read Today, 98-364 (Box 42)
    - Shakespeare's Sonnets: Sexuality, Beauty and the Ravages of Time, 98-365 (Box 42)
    - The Life and Times of Pancho Villa, 98-366 (Box 42)
    - The Public Role of the Humanities tape #1, 98-367/a (Box 42)
    - The Public Role of the Humanities tape #2, 98-367/a (Box 42)
    - The Public Role of the Humanities, 98-367/b (Box 42)
    - The Public Role of the Humanities tape #1, 98-367/c (Box 42)
    - The Public Role of the Humanities tape #2, 98-367/c (Box 42)
    - Telling Other People's Stories: The Ethics of Biography, 99-368 (Box 42)
    - Cultivating Distrust: The Development of Three Cultures of Democracy in America, 99-369/a (Box 42)
    - Trust and Democratic Transition in Contemporary America, 99-369/b (Box 43)
    - The Origins and Decline of the Indus Valley Civilization, 99-370 (Box 43)
    - The Origins of Life, 99-371 (Box 43)
    - Fermat's Last Theorum, 99-372 (Box 43)
    - Who Can Say "Nigger?"... and Other Related Questions, 99-373/a (Box 43)
    - Who Can Say "Nigger?"....and Other Related Questions, 99-373/b (Box 43)
    - The Mathematics of Solitaire, 99-374 (Box 43)
    - Koko Loves: Conversations with a Signing Gorilla, 99-375 (Box 43)
    - American West: The Presence of the Past/California and Dreams of the West, 99-376/a (Box 43)
    - American West: The Presence of the Past "Inventing the West: Buffalo Bill and Frederick Jackson Turner", 99-376/b (Box 43)
    - American West: The Presence of the Past: The Stanfords and the West, 99-376/c (Box 43)
    - Sovereignty and Human Rights, 99-377 (Box 44)
    - Writing Lives: The Uses of Biography, 00-379 (Box 44)
    - Mark Twain and the Holy Land Mania, 00-380 (Box 44)
    - Curating Devi: The Great Goddess, 00-381 (Box 44)
    - Our Obligations to Outsiders: Obligation Beyond National Borders, 00-382/a (Box 44)
    - Our Obligations to Outsiders: Obligations Beyond the Species Boundary, 00-382/b (Box 44)
    - Modern Lessons from Ecological Collapses of Ancient Civilizations, 00-383/a (Box 44)
    - When Do Green Values Pay Off for Big Businesses?, 00-383/b (Box 44)
    - Tangles, Bangles and Knots, 00-384 (Box 44)
    - Logic and Uncertainty in Science and Religion, 00-385 (Box 44)
    - Why Did Human History Unfold Differently on Different Continents for the Past 13,000 Years, 99-378 (Box 44)
    - 20th Century Lives: Saul Bellow, 01-303 (Box 45)
    - Who Goes First? The Story of Self Expirimentation, 01-304 (Box 45)
    - The African Renaissance and the Triple Heritage: Indigenous, Islamic and Westernizing forces, 00-386 (Box 45)
    - Matters of Life and Death: A Jewish Approach to Modern Medical Ethics, 00-387 (Box 45)
    - The Professor and the Madman: The Birth of the Oxford English Dictionary, 00-388 (Box 45)
    - Poetry in the World City: W.H. Auden and the "Great Hotel" of New York, 00-389 (Box 45)
    - The Form of Flight: Auden, Breugel and Abstraction in the 1940's, 00-390 (Box 45)
    - 20th Century Lives: Amir Weiner on Joseph Stalin, 00-391 (Box 45)
    - Human Natures: Genes vs. Cultures, 01-300 (Box 45)
    - Rendezvous With Destiny: Franklin Delano Roosevelt and the Shape of the 20th Century, 01-301 (Box 45)
    - Tanner Lectures in Human Values, 2001: Mean Stories and Stubborn Girls, 01-302/a (Box 45)
    - Tanner Lectures in Human Values, 2001: What It Means to Be Free, 01-302/b (Box 45)
    - Saint Athanasius and Saint Gemara: Interpretation, Tctuality, and the Formation of Christianity and Judaism, 01-398 (Box 46)
    - Democracy and Social Justice: Limits of Contractual Reasoning, 01-393/a (Box 46)
    - Democracy and Social Justice: Democracy and Human Rights, 01-393/b (Box 46)
    - 20th Century Lives: Simone de Beauvoir, 01-394 (Box 46)
    - 20th Century Lives: Gamal Abdul Nasser, 01-395 (Box 46)
    - 20th Century Lives: Rachel Carson, 01-396 (Box 46)
    - 20th Century Lives: Robert Oppenheimer, 01-397 (Box 46)
  - Issues and Ideas
    - Women in Leadership: So Promising a Prospect, So Difficult a Reality, 95-401 (Box 46)
    - Democracy and the Internet, 95-402 (Box 46)
    - Is a Multi-Cultural Democracy Possible?, 95-403 (Box 46)
    - Affirmative Action: The University and Beyond, 95-405 (Box 46)
    - Trial By Media: Reflections on the O.J. Simpson Case, 95-406 (Box 46)
    - The Multicultural Debate: Where Are We Now?, 96-415 (Box 47)
    - Why we need a National Conversation on Race, 96-416 (Box 47)
    - Biodiversity: Going, Going...., 95-407 (Box 47)
    - Visionary Companies, 95-408 (Box 47)
    - The United Nations and the New World Order, 96-409 (Box 47)
    - Economic Changes in Eastern Europe, 96-410 (Box 47)
    - One Big Terrarium, 96-411 (Box 47)
    - Presidential Disability and the Public Interest, 96-412 (Box 47)
    - Social Stratification, Environment and Health, 96-413 (Box 47)
    - Media Mergers and the Public Interest, 96-414 (Box 47)
    - Politics: Up Close and Too Personal, 96-417 (Box 47)
    - History Counts: The Burden of American Politics, 96-418 (Box 47)
    - Style and Substance in Women Business Leaders, 96-419 (Box 48)
    - Where Would Wall Street Be Without the Planet?, 96-420 (Box 48)
    - Silicon Snake Oil: Second Thoughts on the Information Highway, 96-421 (Box 48)
    - Secrets of the Bay, 96-422 (Box 48)
    - How to REALLY Improve Math Education, 96-423 (Box 48)
    - An Evening with Brendan Gill, 96-424 (Box 48)
    - The Workplace of the Future, 96-425 (Box 48)
    - Living with the Enemy (NEVER EDITED), 96-426 (Box 48)
    - Electronic Commerce: What You Need to Know About the World Wide Web, 96-427 (Box 48)
    - The Marriage of Media, 96-428 (Box 48)
    - News of Politics and the Politics of News, 96-429 (Box 48)
    - The Lessons of Bosnia, 96-430 (Box 48)
    - Rethinking Race and Ethnicity: Recent Court Decisions on Affirmative Action, Voting Rights and School Desegregation, 96-431 (Box 49)
    - Assessing the Work of the U.N. War Crimes Tribunals, 96-432 (Box 49)